2 [Music]
ah [applause]
[Music] [Applause]
my mom from you
In this city
[Music] d
[Music] to face
[Music] gives me
lifetime
by me
[Music] makes me laugh
[Music] days
[Music] of my life
9 has james bond
in the ife of this one
pitol it is said is your life
[Applause] [Music]
but this end [Music]
in his vault [Music]
exists
[Music]
maybe with life to live with spray
7 flight I fell asleep
and that day [Music]
to the yes of only 19 villegas
the denouement that I sent tennis and my sister flickr
auto was [Music]
chihuahua chih
like me yes
happened to my lord h
[Music] and about who I am
in that good saying
and music]
of yes
christensen
with my flight
[Music] wore like
sixth
jazz strips naked [Music]
I know who is
[Music] listeners
[Music]
good miami [Music]
efe yes
in English
baby all that you live
with this new 7 price
I won't tell you it was skype fran
under fire he was telling me very skillful laugh
and so after the usual they bring me
before they start and simin is already flickr
de fuego [Music]
or not although I am
[Music]